ustre.am 2016-12-22

# USTREAM - Broadcast Live Streaming Video, Watch Online Events, Chat Live, send a Tweet, follow on Facebook, record your Live Shows

Last Updated: November 17, 2016

Ustream, Inc. ( **“Ustream”** , **“we”** or **“us”** ) provides this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the personal information we receive from users like you when you use our Services (defined in the Terms of Service), whether on our websites, embeddable video players, the Ustream channels, or our software and mobile applications.

As used in this policy, the terms “using” and “processing” information include using cookies on a computer, subjecting the information to statistical or other analysis and using or touching information in any way, including, but not limited to collecting, storing, evaluating, modifying, deleting, using, combining, disclosing and transferring information within the United States or internationally.

### Information Collection and Use

Our primary goals in collecting information are to provide and improve our Services, features and content, to administer your membership and to enable users to enjoy and easily navigate the Site. We also may also use your information in order to better understand how our Services are used.

 _Personally Identifiable Information._

  * In the course of using the Services, we ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you and administer your account ( **“Personal Information”** ). Personal Information may include, but is not limited to, your name, phone number, credit card or other billing information, email address and home and business postal addresses. We use your Personal Information mainly to provide the Services and administer your inquiries.
  * Please be aware that when you register a Ustream account, other users of the Services may be able to see your screen or user name, in addition to any comments or submissions that you post to the Site or submit via the Services. We recommend that you guard your anonymity and sensitive information and that you not use your real name as your screen or user name to the extent that allows others to identify you. If your use of the Services violates or potentially violates Ustream’s Acceptable Use Policy, your Personal Information may be shared with law enforcement and other third parties in accordance with this Privacy Policy and subject to all applicable laws.
  * We also collect other information that you provide as part of your use of the Services, including via your registration and the administration and personalization of your profile webpage (e.g., without limitation zip code, gender, age and individual preferences) ( **“Non-Identifying Information”** ). Certain Non-Identifying Information would be considered a part of your Personal Information if it were combined with other identifiers (for example, combining your zip code with your street address) in a way that enables you to be identified. But the same pieces of information are considered Non-Identifying Information when they are taken alone or combined only with other non-identifying information (for example, your viewing preferences). We may combine your Personal Information with Non-Identifying Information and aggregate it with information collected from other Ustream Users to attempt to provide you with a better experience, to improve the quality and value of the Services and to analyze and understand how our Services are used.
  * We also use your Personal Information to contact you with Ustream newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. Ustream Members who agree to the terms and conditions of the Ustream Terms of Service Agreement are given the opportunity to opt-in to receiving such communications from us in the future. If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such communications from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any of the communications or update your “user preferences” information. (See **“Changing or Deleting Information”** below.)
  * Ustream will also share and use your Personal Information and Non-Identifying Information, either of which may include **“Log Data”** defined below, with other networks, websites and entities affiliated, owned, controlled and/or connected with Ustream, including International Business Machines Corporation and its affiliates. We will use your Personal Information in compliance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.

 _Surveys and Promotions._ From time to time, we may provide you with the opportunity to participate in surveys, contests or sweepstakes (any of these a **“Promotion”** ) via our Services. If you participate in a Promotion we will request certain Personal Information from you. We use the Personal Information you provide to us in these instances to administer your participation in the Promotion. Participation in a Promotion is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information.

 _Log Data._ As you use the Services, whether as a Ustream Member or a non-registered user just browsing (any of these, a **“Ustream User”** ), our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website or information that your mobile device sends when you launch and use the mobile app ( **“Log Data”** ). This log data may include information such as your computer’s IP address, browser type or the domain from which you are visiting or information from your mobile device like screen resolution, device model, carrier and operating system version. We use this information to monitor and analyze use of the Services and for the Site’s technical administration. We do not treat Log Data as Personal Information or use it in association with other Personal Information, though we may aggregate, analyze and evaluate such information for the same purposes as stated above regarding other Non-Identifying Information.

 _Do Not Track._ At this time, there is no formal standard for “do not track” signals and responses. As a result, Ustream does not assign any meaning to potential “do not track” signals. Ustream may receive personally identifiable information about your activity on third party websites in certain circumstances, e.g., if you connect your Ustream account to a social networking service (as described below). Other parties may collect personally identifiable information about your online activities and across third party websites or services when you use the Ustream website or service.

### Cookies

Like many websites, we use “cookies” to collect information. For more information our use of cookies, please see our Cookie Policy.

### Information Sharing and Disclosure

 _Ustream Members._ When you register through the Site and submit your Personal Information to create a profile webpage, Ustream Users will see your screen or user name and the month and year you first registered with Ustream ( **“Required Member Identifiers”** ). You can choose what other Personal Information you provide as part of your profile ( **“Other Member Information”** ) and in some cases you can choose whether to share that information publicly on the Site by making selections via the “user preferences” section of your profile webpage. Providing Other Member Information is voluntary and should correlate with the degree of interaction you want to have with Ustream Users. We recommend that you guard your anonymity and sensitive information.

 _Notifications and Following other Ustream Members._ Ustream Members can also choose to join a “crowd” of other Ustream Members and follow their favorite Ustream broadcaster. If you choose to follow another Ustream Member, you will provide that Ustream Member with your public Ustream identity. By joining the crowd of another Ustream member, you also opt-in for notifications sent to you within the Ustream platform. You may also be followed outside of the Ustream platform, if you expose and make public your identity, email address and social network identity.

 _Aggregate Information and Non-Identifying Information._ We may share aggregated information that includes certain portions of your Non-Identifying Information and Log Data with third parties for industry analysis and demographic profiling and to deliver targeted advertising about other products and services

 _Service Providers._ We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Services, to provide the Services on our behalf, to perform related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Services are used (each a **“Service Provider”** ). The types of Service Providers we use include, without limitation, those that provide the following types of services: credit card processing, accounting, customer relationship management, website maintenance, notification services, database management and analytics. These third parties have access to your Personal Information and Non-Identifiable Information only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

 _SpotXchange._ SpotXchange serves ads on the Site and through the Services and collects information about users’ interaction with those ads, as described in the SpotXchange Privacy Policy, located at <http://www.spotxchange.com/spx_privacypolicy.html>.

 _Third Party Advertising Companies._ We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on the Site and through the Services. These companies may use information about your visits to the Site and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please visit [www.aboutads.info/choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices), [www.networkadvertising.org/choices](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices) and [www.youronlinechoices.com](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/).

 _Third Party Social Networking Services._ As a Ustream Member you can link your account information with certain social networking services (“SNSs”) and broadcast your activities and other data to your friends. In these instances, depending on the “user preferences” you set in your Ustream account, with your permission and on your behalf we will share the information contained in your Ustream account (e.g., Ustream profile page, channel page and any other information you deem public in any content you create on the Site) with the SNS. We also receive certain information (which may include your Personal Information) in accordance with the privacy settings you have set in your SNS account, if any. Other than what we may share with the SNS in connection with your linking of accounts, the personal information a SNS has about you is obtained by the SNS independent of our Services. Other services follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the personal information you submit to them. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other online services you use.

 _Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement._ Ustream cooperates with government and law enforcement officials or private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including but not limited to subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of Ustream or a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical or legally actionable activity.

 _Business Transfers._ Ustream may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including your Personal Information, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy. If Ustream becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, reorganization or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will provide notice to you before your Personal Information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

### Changing or Deleting Your Information

All Ustream Members may review, update, correct or delete the Personal Information in their registration profile by contacting us. If you completely delete all such information, then your account may become deactivated. If you would like us to delete your record in our system, please contact us and we will attempt to accommodate your request. See below for privacy contact information.

### Security

Ustream is very concerned with safeguarding your information. We employ reasonable physical, technological, and administrative security measures and attempt to ensure they are applicable under the circumstances. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

We will make any legally required disclosures of any breach of the security, confidentiality or integrity of your unencrypted electronically stored Personal Data (as defined in applicable state statutes on security breach notification) to you via email or conspicuous posting on this Site in the most expedient time possible and without unreasonable delay, insofar as consistent with (i) the legitimate needs of law enforcement or (ii) any measures necessary to determine the scope of the breach and restore the reasonable integrity of the data system.

### International Transfer

Your information may be transferred to and maintained on computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. If you are located outside the United States and choose to provide information to us, Ustream transfers Personal Information to the United States and processes it there. Your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

### Links to Other Sites

The Services contain links to other websites. If you choose to visit an advertiser by “clicking on” a banner ad or other type of advertisement, or click on another third-party link, you will be directed to that third party’s website. The fact that we link to a website or present a banner ad or other type of advertisement is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party, nor is it an endorsement of their privacy or information security policies or practices. We do not exercise control over third party websites. These other websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. This Privacy Policy addresses the use and disclosure of information that we collect from you through our Services. Other sites follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the personal information you submit to them. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other websites you visit.

### Our Policy Toward Children

We are committed to protecting the safety and privacy of young people using the Internet. We do not knowingly collect personal data from children under age 13. We believe that children should get their parents’ or guardians’ consent before giving out any personal data. If you become aware that we have collected personal data from a child without parental consent, please notify us promptly at [Privacy@ustream.tv](mailto:privacy@ustream.tv). If we become aware that a child under age 13 has provided us with personal data without parental consent, we will take steps to remove such personal data.

If you are a California resident under age 18 and are a registered user of any of the Services, then you may request that we remove any content that you publicly posted on or in the Services. To request removal of such content, please e-mail a detailed description of the specific content to [Privacy@ustream.tv](mailto:privacy@ustream.tv). We reserve the right to request that you provide information that will enable us to confirm that the content that you want removed was created and posted by you.

### Contacting Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [Privacy@ustream.tv](mailto:privacy@ustream.tv) or at:

 _Privacy Matters  
c/o Ustream, Inc.  
410 Townsend Street, Ste 400  
San Francisco, CA 94107_
